[music]
[music] A
new evening in a coffee shop,
thick fog dissolves the houses. [music]
I wander through neighborhoods where memories
drive me crazy.
Where warm spring
covers the soul with winter.
[music]
Where life flew like an arrow past dates, past
us.
[music]
We hoarded papers, forgetting why we
live.
And it always seemed that [the music] was
still playing ahead.
[music]
Only time on loan
gives nothing.
And suddenly [music] cold ice falls on the heart
.
We learn [music] to appreciate when we lose,
when someone's light goes out behind the door.
We wave after the departed trains, trying
[music]
to beg the past for an answer.
We learn to love when it has cooled down, [music]
when there is ash in our palms, and not steel. Oh,
if only I could know in advance [music]
how this transparent sadness would ache in my soul
. He
didn’t say, [music] he didn’t hug, he didn’t have time.
This is an eternal motive. He
saved everything for later and didn’t open his heart to others
. [music]
We fight with the shadow,
[music] we
burn in empty trifles.
And you can’t see how the frost
[music] settles
on our shoulders.
Only happiness is not in the glitter of a shop window,
[music] not in a wad of bills, but in the quiet
truth of loved ones, in their warmth amidst storms. But
we only value what [music] can
no longer be returned.
Continuing on our long
and often [music] meaningless journey,
we learn to appreciate when [music] is lost,
when someone's light goes out behind the door.
We wave after [music] the departed trains,
trying to beg the past for an answer.
We learn to love [music] when it has cooled down,
when there is ashes in our palms, [music] and not
steel. Oh,
if only I could know in advance how
this transparent sadness would ache in my soul.
Call the old folks, hug them,
[music]
while the pulse beats.
Let the grievances pass, I pray for this today
.
[music]
Because all the songs have the
same ending.
[singing]
We [music] remain in the memory of forgotten milestones, we
sit.
[music]
We learn to appreciate when we lose,
when someone's light goes out behind the door [music]
.
We wave after the departed trains, trying to
beg the past for an answer.
We learn to love, [music]
when it has cooled down, when there are ashes and
broken [music] crystal in our palms. We should take care of what we
have while we are here, before the
soul [music] flies away into the distance.
[music]